matchpoint.com 2013-06-08

# Matchpoint

**PRIVACY POLICY**

We respect your privacy and take our responsibility to protect your personal information very seriously.

The information we learn from you helps us personalize and continually improve your experience with us and our providers.

**INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE IT**

1. Your name and email address.

We collect your name and your email address so that we can forward messages to you from providers that are competing for your business and so that providers can contact you with offers in response to your inquiries. We also use this information to keep track of offers and services that may be or are actually provided to you by Company.com or other providers.

2. Zip code.

We collect your zip code so that we can match you with local providers in your area.

3. Other data.

While your email address and zip code are the only pieces of information required to use the Company.com service, we will often present you with other optional form fields such as age, income range, specific needs, etc. in order for you to narrow your search for providers. When you choose to provide this information to us, we will use it to match you with specific providers who are looking for interested consumers with that profile. In such cases, we will send the optional data to the provider, along with your Company.com email address and your zip code, so that they can deliver customized messages to you regarding your inquiry and in order for them to evaluate the performance of their campaigns with Company.com.

4. Non-Personally Identifiable Information (Non-PII).

Like most standard website servers, we use log files to collect Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, and date/time stamp. We use the information to analyze site usage, administer the site, understand usage and navigation trends in aggregate, and determine the relevance of content.

When you respond to or view a Company.com form or visit the Company.com site, we place a cookie that assigns an anonymous, unique identifier to the end user?s Internet browser. Cookies are small data files commonly used on the Internet to help optimize and personalize the Internet end user experience and identify repeat visitors to websites. These cookies are not used to collect any personally identifiable information such as name, address, social security number, etc.

These Cookies help us to personalize your experience and to pay providers that refer users to Company.com. We may retain ad delivery and reporting data that is necessary for accounting and audit purposes.

**ADDITIONAL INFORMATION SHARING**

In addition to the sharing of personal information as set forth above, Company.com only shares personal information with other companies or individuals outside of Company.com in the following limited circumstances:

  * We provide such information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.
  * We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service or Terms of Use, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Company.com, its users or the public as required or permitted by law, (e) provide our services, including the display of customized content and advertising, (f) audit, research and analyze in order to maintain, protect and improve our services, or (g) develop new services.

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page, and such changes will become effective when posted.

If you have any additional questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us any time through this website.
